(Amy:)Penny said she's not sure she wants
to be Leonard's girlfriend anymore.
(Sheldon:)Wrong. She just took a sip
from his Diet Dr. Pepper.
(Amy:)So?
(Sheldon:)So if she wants to end her pair-bond
with Leonard...
(Sheldon:)...why on earth would she guzzle
a witch's brew of his soda and spit?
(Amy:)It's complicated.
(Sheldon:)String Theory is complicated.
(Sheldon:)That's just yucky.
(Sheldon:)Don't get any ideas.
(Sheldon:)All right, for the sake of argument,
let's say that's true.
(Sheldon:)Why doesn't Penny just end
the relationship?
(Amy:)She's not sure how she feels.
(Sheldon:)How can she not be sure
how she feels?
(Sheldon:)You know, when I have a feeling,
I know it.
(Sheldon:)Trains? Love them.
(Sheldon:)Swordfish? I love them too.
(Sheldon:)They're fish with a sword for a nose.